Shannon Armor

123 Main Street, Santa Clarita, CA 12345 \$.armor@youremail.com (123) 456-7890

Attentive child care professional with over seven years of experience in caring for infants, toddlers, and preschoolers. Excellent at devising interesting educational and recreational activities for children of all ages. Knowledge of child care techniques and a proven track record of creating a fun and safe environment for children. Fluent in Spanish and English.

Education

Associates Degree in Early Childhood Education

Santa Clarita Community College Santa Clarita, Ca, September 2012 -June 2014

Key Skills

- Friendly
- Excellent communication
- Organized
- Safety management
- Activity planning

Certifications

American Red CrossJune 2020

- First Aid
- Infant CPR
- CPR
- AED

Professional Experience

Child Care Provider

Santa Clarita Department of Family Support Services, Santa Clarita, CA | September 2016 - Present

- Collaborate with 17 other child care providers to ensure that all children are safe and receiving a professional level of care
- Provide safe and efficient child care services for up to 50 children from six weeks to 11 years of age
- Create fun indoor and outdoor activities and projects for the children
- Develop relationships with the children, assist those who are going through difficult times, and connect them with additional professional help if needed

Child Care Assistant

Happy Babies DayCare, Santa Clarita, CA | June 2014 - September 2016

- Provided child care services to upto 15 babies aged six weeks to 18 months
- Daily tasks included feeding, changing, and bathing the babies
- Created fun age-appropriate games and tasks for the children